[{"answer": "I see", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, it's a small place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "The Welsh poet my friend drank himself to death at the that place half an hour after losing a sock in this very dryer", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Are you abusing the tour to stalk me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "They were going to install giant legs so if a plane was flying at the tower it could run away. But where's it going to run", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It'd have to jump in the that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, give me strength! A my frien", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What have you always wanted to do", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Every date will be our honeymoon", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Let's knock our heads together and find a way to stop her loving me....Got it! We'll tell her I'm on the sex offenders register....No, I am and she knows.  Joke, sorry. Ah. We'll say I'm gay! I did once dabble actually, so I can tell a plausible story", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "One Moslem doesn't make a mosque, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You made love to a guy", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You made love to a Moslem? 38", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "One Moslem doesn't make a mosque, my friend", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, sir, it was Prince my friend and he made love to me. The fact that it took three bottles of poppers and a Jacuzzi full of my friend to loosen me up confirmed my heterosexuality", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Just fascinated. 59", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You're good at fascinating", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend? What are you doing there", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "She's had quite a few headaches lately", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Good afternoon, my friend. Is my friend here? 79", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I must be", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Crowded field, writing. 89", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "We all know who's seen her potential", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Shut up! We're getting married", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And you think I love you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Wouldn't I? You crushed me", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Bullshit. You wanted to stop me being a lesbian", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "OW! Stop it! Why are you doing that", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, you keep still", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You've never earned that title. I wouldn't fake it with my friend. I won't with you", "docId": "Arthur.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 32}]